Hare no chi ame hiroi uchuu
晴
れ
の
ち
雨
広
い
宇
宙
Rain follows the clear sky, across an expansive universe
Mata hitotsu motsureau keiyaku ga
ま
た
一
つ
も
れ
合
う
契
約
が
As yet another entangled contract
Hikari sae mo koete shimau
光
さ
え
も
超
え
て
し
ま
う
Surpasses even light itself
Asu no kagaku wa mahou nano ka?
明
日
の
科
学
は
魔
法
な
の
か
？
Will tomorrow's science become as magic?
Sore wa aru hi totsuzen seijaku naru uchuu ni
そ
れ
は
あ
る
日
突
然
静
寂
な
る
宇
宙
に
It's a fear like the dread of floating
Ishiki dake ga tadayou youna kyoufu
意
識
だ
け
が
漂
う
よ
な
恐
怖
In a silent universe as naught but mind
Kono mi wa ryuushi ni natte
こ
の
身
は
粒
子
に
な
っ
て
If this body dusts away to particles
Yakume wo oeru youni
役
目
を
終
え
る
よ
う
に
And finds its mission complete
Kazoekirenai pixel wa
数
え
切
れ
な
い
ピ
ク
セ
ル
は
Will those countless pixels
Tsugi no tabi wo mezasu no ka
次
の
旅
を
目
指
す
の
か
Set off on their next pilgrimage?
Taiyou no dance sakujozumi no meta-reference
太
陽
の
ダ
ン
ス
削
除
済
み
の
Beneath her dancing Sun, a deleted meta-reference
メ
タ
リ
フ
ァ
レ
ン
ス
Rikai sae oyobanai door real he no kanshou
理
解
さ
え
及
ば
な
い
ド
ア
Beyond the door defying our understanding, interfering with the real
リ
ア
ル
へ
の
干
渉
Jikuu seiritsu saseru ENIAC
時
空
成
立
さ
せ
る
エ
ニ
ア
ッ
ク
Space-time breathed to life by the ENIAC
Ranzatsu ni hanatareta mama tsukamenai jikan no ya
乱
雑
に
放
た
れ
ま
Fired haphazardly, time's arrow slips by ungrasped
つ
か
め
な
い
時
間
の
矢
Suusen oku wo koeru heiretsu shori
数
千
億
を
超
え
る
並
列
処
理
Through hundreds of billions of parallel processors
Kakikae no dekinai mirai nara
書
き
換
え
の
出
来
な
い
未
来
な
ら
If this future isn't overwritten, it's
Game over
ゲ
|.
ム
オ
|.
バ
Game over